Let's start the second game I'm losing 0
-1 I need to
pop off Okay,
so this is just South Africa, right?
But
where? Might be something like.. Closer to
Eswatini
Lesotho We have some mountains over there
Yeah, I'm gonna send something like here
Oh no,
definitely not East London Next round
we have tracker
No, this
is just a car
And in water
okay so the hills look Colombian
I think
but it also might be Mexico
where is the Sun Sun is to the Sun
is saying nothing
it's not good
okay so it's gonna be a 50
-50 I guess between Colombia and Mexico
but my first thought was Colombia
so I'm gonna go here I thin
k It can be Yucatan,
it can be Campeje in Mexico,
but I'm going Colombia Let's see
Yeah, it was Nordele Colo
Not good
I should have committed more towards
north
I think it was a
mistake
but it's fine now
we have Ghana
probably nothing
some red dirt and we have some hills
I think Kumasi should be a good Good
guess over here
I think Okay,
we are fine
Next round
We
have English language
We have some weird.. weird architecture
What is this car?
Is this a tracker?
This is no way
This is some kind of island
But I have no idea.. Okay,
with this sign.. Like
can it be like
one of islands close to Australia
I think
But which ones? Wait
No for sure
not this one
Like what else? Like we have
some kind of mixed American plus
Australian style here
What can it be?
Oh, wait,
maybe it's might be
the Christmas Island,
I think, or Cocos,
one of those two Oh, y
eah, that makes sense
But which one? Wait
So Christmas Island have this car
with like a black ending
But Cocos also have a specific car
And we have nothing over here
This is super weird
I've never seen anything like this
Okay, I'm gonna go between, I think
Like between those two
Because picking
one is actually maybe not a good idea
I'm gonna play defensive here Yes,
I'm gonna go betw
een those two Yeah, okay,
it was Christmas Island Sheesh
He knew it
That's unlucky
Next we
have India
Okay with these polls
Okay
so I think this should be Southern I
ndia I unfortunately do not know the poll here
But yeah,
it's definitely southern
part of the India,
like maybe Karnataka, closer to Bengaluru
Can I see a bridge here?
We have mountains over there,
so maybe it makes sense
So I'm going to send something like this
maybe Like here
Yeah, let's just send
Oh, really nice
That's a huge damage And I won Nah, 1k
more 1k more, okay
So I can win I think I can win thi
s I just need a good rounds like this one
We have Greece, Greek language
We have a bay to the west
It should be just mainland
I
think I'm gonna send something like here
Okay, it was just a creepy island
It's still okay
though I just need small countries
and I can win
Okay, we have Poland
Probably just central Poland,
I think M
aybe more closer to the north,
I'm gonna come here
I think
Oh
no,
there's no way It was just southern
Poland Next round,
we
have Baltics, like Estonia or Latvia
I think Maybe Lithuania
also, we don't have Poles
That's not good
Okay,
so I'm not sure about the country here
So
I'm just gonna go in middle to the Latvia
and hope it's like close
Because we don't have any.. Okay,
maybe we have.. No, it's just trees
Yeah, so I think it should be fi
ne
It was just Estonia
Not good Next round
Okay so this should be
with this car
New Zealand Should be Northern Ireland
I think Yes
let me just send like something like this
hope
it's not gonna be the southern island
because i am dead if it is so y
eah okay
it's fine you can get some damage here
next round
we have a
mexican Wait,
it's not Mexico
It's Romanian,
I think Taxi Maybe it's not a taxi
I thought
in the first instance it's Mexico,
but we definitely are not in Mexico
We have European architecture
Really nice bridge
Probably Romania
Yeah, it should be Romania
Okay, can we find this? Like I have
vibes like here
maybe Are there any bridges over there?
Hmm Doesn't look like there is
a bridge here
Oh, maybe this one?
Let's check the angle
No, it's definitely not this one
It can be border with Bulgaria
I think I'm not,
I don't think I can find this one
It's gonna be fine to find
I guess
Oh it w
as there He got it
Oh no,
that's not good
I can't lose
this Okay
We have Ireland
or UK Okay
so this is UK
We have big hills in the back
So can it be Scotland?
So I think it's Scotland
actually The architecture kind of fits
Yeah, I'm gonna go Scotland right now
Maybe like.. huh Something like there?
No, I don't think so
I think it's more outskirts area
I'm gonna go here
Yeah, nice!
And we won!
That's a GG 1
1 -1, bounce
back